<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#style">
	<head>
		<layout/>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div xml:id="captions">
			<p begin="00:00:02" end="00:00:07">I found it very hard to deal with. Mark had a breakdown when he was 18.</p>
			<p begin="00:00:07.7" end="00:00:09.8">The old brother had this problem.</p>
			<p begin="00:00:10" end="00:00:16.3">He was our problem and family, Mon, Dad, Police did not know what to do with him.</p>
			
			<p begin="00:00:20.8" end="00:00:29">There are more than 100,000 people with schizophrenia in Australia. Yet the illness really features in the Media.</p>
			<p begin="00:00:29.8" end="00:00:33">"Mom and Dad had to put up with it for another 20 years.</p>
			<p begin="00:00:33.2" end="00:00:37.6">We weren't able to escape because nobody knew how to deal with this issue."</p>
			<p begin="00:00:38.5" end="00:00:45">Schizophrenia is a biological disease of the brain which permanently disables more young people</p>
			<p begin="00:00:45.1" end="00:00:52">than any other illness. Yet it receives far less public attention than any other serious disease.</p>
			<p begin="00:00:54.4" end="00:01:02">Schizophrenia often appears during teenage years and causes 10% of the patients to commit suicide.</p>
			<p begin="00:01:03" end="00:01:09.5">This accounts for a grater number of deaths than from aids, Multiple sclerosis and melanoma combined.</p>
			<p begin="00:01:11" end="00:01:15">Yet, no nation wide public awareness campaign has ever appeared.</p>
			<p begin="00:01:18.6" end="00:01:27.5">90% of cases arise in families with no previous history of mental illness so every child is at risk.</p>
			<p begin="00:01:28" end="00:01:34">Sooner or later one in every 100 children will be diagnosed with schizophrenia.</p>
			<p begin="00:01:35" end="00:01:42">Many patients refuse to take medication which makes it difficult for their families to take care of them at home.</p>
			<p begin="00:01:42.3" end="00:01:49">This is also why around 25% of street people in our cities are Schizophrenia patients.</p>
			<p begin="00:01:50" end="00:01:54.7">"In this country hundreds more people have been diagnosed with schizophrenia every year.</p>
			<p begin="00:01:55" end="00:02:00.3">We don't know how to take it before happens how to cure it after it happens.</p>
			<p begin="00:02:00.8" end="00:02:07.2">The only long term answer is to find a way to prevent it and cure it and that is what NISAD</p>
			<p begin="00:02:07.5" end="00:02:12.3">The Neuro Science institute of Schizophrenia  and Allied Disorders is all about.</p>
			<p begin="00:02:13.2" end="00:02:19">"Nisad has developed a new concept in scientific research. We aren't all located in one building.</p>
			<p begin="00:02:19.2" end="00:02:21.2">We are a virtual institute.</p>
			<p begin="00:02:21.5" end="00:02:27.8">This means we work with the most talented scientists internations throughout Australia and around the world.</p>
			<p begin="00:02:28.3" end="00:02:35">  Our vision is to discover the causes of Schizophrenia and we use a range of multi facetted approaches.</p>
			<p begin="00:02:35.3" end="00:02:39">Our researches use a lot of different methods as you will see.</p>
			<p begin="00:02:40.1" end="00:02:45.2">"We've shown for the first time that the reception for a particular chemical within the brain</p>
			
			<p begin="00:02:45.4" end="00:02:49">is altered in the frontal lobs of the brain in schizophrenia.</p>

			<p begin="00:02:49.2" end="00:02:54.3">With more research into why these dangers occur we had to go on a better understanding into</p>
			<p begin="00:02:54.4" end="00:03:02">what causes schizophrenia which is essential for the development of better treatments in the future.</p>-->
		</div>
	</body>
</tt>
